smspunch.com 2016-05-07

# |FREE SMS To Pakistan | Ufone | Warid | Moblilnk | Zong | Telenor | Send Free SMS | SMS PUNCH : Policy

## Privacy Policy

SMS Punch understands the importance of your privacy. At SMS Punch we are committed to protecting the privacy of our users. If and when SMS Punch collects personal identifying information, we maintain the confidentiality, security and integrity of that personal information obtained from our users. We do not share nor disclose personal information to any party beyond the SMS Punch network. For your own protection, please review the following terms and conditions before joining SMS Punch. We want you to enjoy SMS Punch to the fullest, but we also want you to stay informed. Through subscribing to SMS Punch, you are agreeing to our terms and conditions.

**Terms and Conditions of Use**  
Your use of SMS Punch.com, the SMS Punch Mobile means that you agree to the terms and conditions outlined below. We reserve the right to change, modify and or remove portions of these terms at any time. If you choose to continue your use of this site after we have posted changes to the terms, it means you have accepted those terms. SMS Punch will not share your email address with anyone else without your permission.

**What kind of information does SMS Punch request and why is it necessary?**  
All identifying information SMS Punch requests from the user is strictly kept confidential within the SMS Punch network in encrypted format (no human eye can read the encrypted items). Personally identifying information SMS Punch asks for includes: your name, mobile phone and e-mail address. When you register as a member of SMS Punch, we ask for your honest responses to this information so that we can serve you more efficiently and effectively. SMS Punch will not sell, rent nor disclose any of this personal information without your prior notification or consent.

**Does SMS Punch protect my privacy?**  
Your SMS Punch account is password-protected, meaning only you have access to your account-related information. If you refrain from sharing your password with others, you can help us to continue this security and confidentiality. Remember to log out of your SMS Punch account when you are finished. By doing so, you protect your information from being re-opened by another person if you are using a shared or public computer. Please note that neither SMS Punch nor any other Internet service can promise complete privacy. The Internet is not yet 100% secure, therefore it is recommended that you take care with the information you choose to provide on any online service.

**My Outgoing and incoming Messages data is secure?**  
Any information/content that is sent or received to/from SMS Punch for sms text messaging and/or storage purposes will remain the property of the User. SMS Punch will at no time collect or redistribute this information, except where legally required by law, FIA or other agencies to do so. This has particular reference to any messages database, numbers and/or recipient details that you may deliver to us, or store on our databases. SMS Punch is not responsible, nor liable, for your actions while using our site. As the user, you are required to accept total responsibility for your behavior and conduct while using SMS Punch. If you do not agree to follow SMS Punch's Terms and Conditions, please refrain from entering our site. Common courtesy and mutual respect are necessary when communicating with other members of SMS Punch. Because SMS Punch hopes to promote a safe and fun atmosphere for our users, please read over the following list of what actions you agree to refrain from while using SMS Punch and its properties:  
* Sending, sharing, promoting, or advertising harmful or illegal material.  
* Encouraging or manipulating the dispersal of content in the form of: a threat, harassment, ethnic slander, sexual misconduct, or inappropriate and unwanted behavior towards another member.  
* Acting in a manner that is potentially abusive or insensitive to other SMS Punch members. This includes: harassing, threatening, embarrassing, or intentionally harming another user.  
* Attempting to gain account information, private profiles or a password from another SMS Punch member. Obtaining email addresses, cell phone numbers or any other private member information without prior consent is strictly forbidden.  
* Assuming the identity of any individual other than yourself. You may not impersonate another member, or a SMS Punch staff member.  
* Posting or exchanging defamatory, abusive, slanderous, harmful, promotional or unsolicited material. SMS Punch holds the right to eliminate and remove any content that may violate these terms.  
* Stalking of other members and SMS Punch staff is a serious act and in some instances it is a crime. This includes repetitive calling, e-mailing, or initiating non-consensual contact of any kind. SMS Punch reserves the right to inform authorities of these violations if we feel it necessary.  
* Copying or replicating the intellectual work of any SMS Punch member, or any works you may find on this site. We respect, and wish to protect the rights and property of our users; we expect you to do the same.

**Anti Spam Policy** Any registered User of SMS Punch can send sms text messages to his/her friends, family, colleagues, clients, contacts etc using the SMS Punch Interface. These interface conditions of use strictly forbid spamming to cell phone Users. We have several software filters to block spam messages. However, we cannot guarantee that spamming will not ever occur. Please let us know, (click on the contact link above for details) the details of the message like content of message, time of delivery, sender name or number etc so that we can immediately check and block the user responsible for the same.

**Limits on our Abilities**  
Although your privacy is our top priority, due to the existing statutory, legal and technical environment, we are unable to ensure that personally identifiable information of our Users will not be disclosed to third parties in ways that are not described in this policy. Additionally, we may (and here you give us authorization to) disclose any private information about you to private entities, law enforcement or other government officials, which we may believe to be necessary at our sole discretion or appropriate to address or to resolve inquiries or problems. We undertake that this will not be done for commercial purposes or for our personal gain.

If you have any further questions about our privacy and anti-spam policy or about its implementation, please contact us You hereby acknowledge that the acceptance of this privacy policy is a condition to your use of our products and services and that you agree to be bound by all of our Terms and Conditions.

**Copyright Rules**  
Everything contained within this site is owned by SMS Punch or used with permission. If you wish to retransmit, use or copy any information for this site, you must have our explicit written permission. Ownership or permission must be gained if you wish to change or advertise anything from SMS Punch. Violators of this policy will be dealt with in a serious and legal manner.

* * *

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We also use third party advertisements on our site to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geo targeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.
